Next, I will explain the difference between the sewing line type by another small case.
First, create a square board to make it flat and simulated on the ground.
Cut a board to the outer layer.
Copy and paste the current board.
You can see that the pattern is TURN.
We manually change one of them to CUSTOM ANGLE.
You can notice that after changing to CUSTOM ANGLE, the effect of the sewing line folding angle will automatically expand.
There is no pressure before this.
Next, we select the board and apply positive and negative pressure according to the direction of the pattern.
If the direction of the pattern is facing the outside, use the positive pressure.
If the direction of the pattern is facing the inside, use the negative pressure.
This is because the positive pressure is from the inside to the outside, and the negative pressure is from the outside to the inside.
You can see that the effect of setting the sewing line as CUSTOM ANGLE and TURN will be significantly different.
After opening the surface of the thick pattern, TURN will also have an obvious folding effect.
The value of the bending strength of the fabric will also affect it.
The harder the fabric, the more obvious the sewing line type and folding angle effect will be.
The fabric used at the time was a relatively hard leather.
Now we switch it to a softer default fabric.
After simulation, we can see that the shape of the two pillows will be similar.
But the performance at the seam of the sewing line is still different.
The sewing line is the same as the sewing line at the beginning.
The sewing line is the same as the sewing line at the end.
The sewing line that is shown as CUSTOM ANGLE is the sewing line effect of the hair line.
And TURN is two pieces of pattern.
So there will be an obvious layer relationship.
You need to remember that torrents will calculate the conflict thickness of two panels and the thickness of the fabric, so there will be obvious gaps.
Thanks for watching!